mpaymall.com 2012-12-01

# mPayMall

At mPayMall, we are committed to protecting your privacy online. Below is a brief overview of the highlights of our Privacy Policy. This will give you a summary sketch about how information is collected from you and how it is used.

 **Information Collected**

When you shop on our site, we collect personal information from you such as your name, e-mail address, shipping address, telephone number, product selections, credit card or other payment information. We may also collect, or our third party ad server and content server will collect the URL you came from, IP address, domain types (e.g. .com or .org, etc.), your browser type, the country, state and telephone area code where your server is located, the pages of our site that were viewed during a visit.

We do not sell or rent your personal information to others. We use customer information we collect only for the purposes of filling orders, contacting purchasers to inform them of their order status, sending promotional information, enhancing the operation of our site, for statistical purposes and to administer our systems. We may use third parties to help us fulfill orders, to help process payments, to provide customer service, to serve site content, and to help administer promotional emails. We give them access to the information needed to do their job. Sometimes that includes your personal information. Our computer system protects personal information using advanced firewall technology.

You do not have to worry about receiving unsolicited email from other companies or individuals as a result of shopping at our site. We do, on occasion, send out an email announcement to inform our customers when we add a major new feature to our website; once again, those email addresses are not shared with anyone else.

 **Credit Card Transactions**

mPayMall offers security by using Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) technology on our site. The secure server software encrypts the credit card information you input before it is forwarded to us, preventing others from accessing your private information during the process.

 **When you request a login name**

You can choose a login name and password when you place an order online. This will enable online order tracking and allow us to save your customer information so you won't have to re-enter it every time you place an order. Before you choose a login name, you must provide us with your name, mailing address, and e-mail address. We use this information to authenticate your identity whenever you request access to these special online services.

 **When you leave our site**

We have no control over the privacy practices of sites outside our domain. If you follow a link to another Web site, read the site's privacy policy and contact the site's administrator with your privacy-related questions.
